Trixie, I need your help. No, she's
lying. Listen to me. Trixie, Trixie,
listen to me. My emergency is bigger.
>> My emergency is an actual emergency.
Sheesh. Girls, one at a time. Fractured
you first. Okay, so it's career day at
school tomorrow and every pony has to
bring a parent to talk about what they
do for work and Trixie pick me. I was
still talking. Shut up. Please be my
career day, Mom. Um, I'm right here if
anyone cares.
>> Why doesn't the great and powerful
Trixie go with one of you and the other
one simply brings sparkle?
>> No way. It would be too embarrassing.
>> Yeah, she's the boring one.
>> No, I'm not. Tomorrow is my six-hour
long bookshelf organization fan club.
And just today, we reorganized every
bookshelf in the town library
alphabetically by both author and
subject. Perfect. Then I'll be
Fractured's career day, Mom, and you'll
be flawless.
>> Oh, how fun. This will be a pleasant way
to spend some quality time together as a
family. Eskimo kisses.
I'll have to put my next book club
meeting on hold, but that's all right.
Maybe I can get in touch with Miss
Cheerly and surprise the students with a
spontaneous pop quiz. I always loved
those as a Philly. [screaming]
[snorts]
Upsy Daisy. You two. You wouldn't want
to be late for school, would you?
>> Shut the hell up, [__] Flawless, wake
your ass up. It's time for school.
I want my own bed. I can't keep living
like this where she blasts major ass in
my face every morning.
>> Aw, terrible. How terrible.
>> Fractured. I get where you're coming
from, but money is tight right now.
Yeah, and Trixie just lost her job
again. I don't remember anyone asking
for your input, [__]
>> Well, bunk beds are going for pretty
cheap right now. Why don't we pick up
one of those?
>> You know, they'll just fight over the
top bunk.
>> We won't fight. Promise.
>> Yeah, we're not little kids. We aren't
going to fight over some stupid bed.
>> Totally.
>> If you two don't cut it out, we're
returning it.
That's probably the $2,000 bulk of
physical PlayStation games Trixie bought
from Fluttershy.
Just put it on the floor and Trixie
shall pick it up. Trixie doesn't want to
risk grazing your hoof because that
would be gay.
>> Don't you play on Xbox?
>> These are investments for PlayStation is
killing physical media.
>> They can reverse their decision.
>> They won't. Okay, put then in the corner
of the living room with your popcorn
buckets and law boos.
>> You mock me, but that corner of the room
is worth like eight bucks. I hope you're
so mad. No, really. I hope it makes you
so mad that I spend money on worthless
[__] This is such [__] I lived in
this house way longer than you. I
deserve that top bunk. Go to sleep.
Career day is in 25 minutes and I need
to be fully awake for my standing
ovation after Trixie blows the class
away with her magical talents. Hell
yeah. With the top, I get the AC all to
myself. It feels so good. And it's so
warm, it almost makes me have to piss.
Well, I suppose the bottom bunk isn't so
bad. At least I don't have to deal with
her anymore. Oh, dear God.
Mom,
what's the matter now?
>> Fractured is pissing herself, and now
the piss is seeping through the bed and
falling on my face.
>> Fractured? Is this true?
>> I am literally drenched in piss. I
didn't do it on purpose.
>> Fractured. If you're really too lazy to
go to the bathroom, find a corner of the
room, and pee there like normal ponies.
Why does this house always wreak of
piss?
Where do you think you're going?
>> I'm going to take a fat piss in the
toilet.
>> Whatever. I'm going back to sleep. Don't
wake me up with your fat butt cheeks
clapping when you walk back in.
>> Holy crap. I like totally almost died
just now. Bunk beds are really scary.
>> You want me on the top bunk?
>> Just for now. Not because I'm scared of
it or anything.
>> Whatever. I don't really care.
>> Now, nothing can hurt me while I'm down
here.
You broke the bunk bed. I am still
highly traumatized.
>> It's because Flawless is getting fat.
>> None of my diets work, which is probably
just God's way of saying I'm cute just
the way I am.
>> In that case, Flawless, I have a
surprise for you.
>> Oh, boy. Jelly donuts.
>> No, it's a stability ball that will help
you lose weight. You use it to increase
the intensity of exercises by creating
an unstable surface which forces more
muscle engagement to burn more calories.
Later, fat ass. We're going to get Long
John Silvers before school because I'm
not as fat as you are.
>> Hey, this isn't so hard. Actually, I bet
I could go even tighter.
Look, Scootaloo, it's Rainbow Dash.
>> Hi, Rainbow Dash.
>> Hey, Squirt. What's up? I'm just taking
a big smelly [__]
>> We're holding a meeting about how cool
you are. Do you want to come up here and
join us?
>> No.
>> Okay. Well, I just wanted to let you
know that it's career day at school
today.
>> Don't say anymore, [__] I get the
picture. You do. Og Rainbow Dash, I knew
you would understand. Are you sure you
don't want to come up here and be our
special guest for the Rainbow Dash fan
club meeting?
>> Yeah.
>> Where the hell is Trixie? She was
supposed to be here hours ago.
>> She'll turn up. I'm sure she just got
held up with [music] something
important.
Yes, cook, my darlings. Soon you shall
be in mama's belly.
>> Oh my god,
>> Sparkle. Did you know Manic could run as
fast [music] as Sonic?
>> What? No, he can't.
>> Manic has no special skill. That's like
his whole thing.
>> I am literally watching him run in
[music] an episode. He's leaving a green
trail and everything. The animators drew
that [__]
>> Then you raise your leg up like this.
And that's how you do the splits.
>> Whatever. Where the hell are you?
>> I'm doing something important.
>> More important than your own daughter's
career day presentation.
>> Unless you forgot I'm a unicorn fat ass.
When the time comes, the great and
powerful Trixie will get there quickly
with her splendid unicorn magic.
>> You better not be eating pizza rolls.
Now, don't call me again. I got like 2
minutes of data left, which you are
paying for, by the way.
>> Look, there's my friends and their
sisters. I'm going to go say hi.
>> It is rather admirable of you to show up
for Scootaloo on career day. But are you
sure you are fit for the task?
>> Yeah, I'm basically her cool mom.
Hey, want to watch me crack open this
can of tomatoes between my butt cheeks?
It will be like V8 juice, but instead of
eight different vegetables, it will be
tomato juice and [__] If I poured it
into some glasses and pass the cups
around to the Phillies and Colts, that
would be funny. Oh, Dash, these antics
of yours are quite concerning. Are you
sure your reckless history of being a
terrible pony no one likes equals ideal
parentage?
>> Hey, Rarity, your costume looks funny.
>> This is my new creation, darling. As a
seamstress, I must always look my best.
Oh, I thought you were trying to look
bad.
>> God damn it. Why is she here?
>> Hey, Scootaloo. I showed up like a
responsible adult like you wanted me to
do.
>> No, I was going to ask you not to come
because everyone in class thinks you're
a loser.
>> No, they [music] don't. They think I'm
awesome.
>> You eat junk food and play video games
all day.
>> Damn, I sound [music] like a badass.
>> All the other kids have real parents
listing them. I don't want some washed
up 35year-old athlete who smells like
Cool Ranch Doritos.
>> Oh my god. [laughter]
>> Oh my goodness. Open it so I can
reattach her arms with magic. Give it a
few minutes. I want her to simmer in the
pain for calling me a loser.
>> [__] your job is moving clouds for $7
an hour Monday through Friday. That's
basically the equivalent of working at
Burger King. I just I wanted her to know
I was there for her.
>> You cut her arms off.
Lunchtime, every pony, go out to the
playground and eat with your mommies and
daddies. And then we'll begin the career
day presentations.
>> Hey, Applejack, what did you bring for
lunch? Why, I brought a [__] ton of
apples. Because that's all Granny Smith
allows the Apple family to eat. Besides
each other's ass since we're all about
that incest [__] Apple Bloom loves
apples. Don't you, Apple Bloom?
>> With that many apples, I bet your poop
must taste like apples, too. Haha.
>> Rainbow watching out for Scoots. The
three of us here. And Pinkie Pie is
running her very own cake shop with Mrs.
Cakes. Isn't it so cool how every member
of the main six has full-time jobs now
with children to look after? We really
are all growing up and becoming
hardworking citizens of society.
Is that your lunch? Yeah, Trixie put it
together for me. This is all junk food.
What happened to the yogurt packet and
fresh berries I packed for you? Who
wants to eat berries over pixie sticks
and chicken nugies? The other kids are
right about you. You're lame.
fractured. That's stealing. Who taught
you how to do that?
>> Trixie,
>> you can't just eat a Twinkies for lunch.
You need protein, like meat.
What's gotten into her? She's hunting
for meat, like you asked.
I never told her to hunt children. Who
knew raising multiple kids would be this
much of a hassle? Oh, I wish Trixie
would hurry up.
I didn't realize raising two children at
once would be this tiresome.
>> Well, it's not like you and Shining
Armor were much different.
>> No, I was very well behaved and I
respected authority.
>> Really? Because I seem to remember
spending 2 days [music] building you a
brand new bookshelf and you started
crying because it wasn't perfectly
symmetrical with [music] the rest of the
furniture in your room.
>> That happened one time.
>> My point is, you weren't nearly as easy
to raise as you might think. Do you
remember your own career day in the
fifth grade? You were supposed to bring
a parent and your father volunteered.
You locked yourself in your bedroom and
you told us [crying] your life was
ruined because you wanted Princess
[music] Celestia to come instead.
>> Well, that's different because Princess
Celestia [music] was a princess and dad
is ugly as [__]
>> Twilight, are [music] you not the same?
>> Thanks for being no help at all, [__]
And by the way, I would return that
yellow sundress back to whichever
Goodwill you thrifted it from cuz it
makes your saggy but look gross.
Oh no. What time is it? [__] I slept
through nearly the whole school day.
Hopefully there's still time. Wait a
second. This is Flawless and Fractured's
underwear. Were they in such a hurry
they forgot to put them on before
leaving for school?
>> Someone stole your underwear. Well, we
aren't wearing them, so clearly someone
must have stolen them.
>> Mine would sell for a high price, so I
guess I can understand why someone would
steal them.
>> Well, I guess I'll be on the lookout for
suspicious individuals. The two of you
just focus on your presentations for
now. Oh, yeah. I'm going to need some
information first.
What kind of panties do you wear?
>> Okay, Flawless. It would seem like next
it's our turn. You're going to love what
I have planned. No, I already told you
that you're boring. I wanted Trixie to
be here. Flawless. I know I might not be
the parent you wanted, but I'm trying my
best. Please, all I ask is that you give
this purple pony with a fat dump truck a
chance.
>> A
Oh my god. Is that a Hatsune Q concert?
Hey, Rainbow Dash. What are you doing
here? Sup, [music] [__] I just thought
I'd waste some time here since Scootala
doesn't want my ass around. Okay.
>> Hey, girls. [music] I didn't expect to
see you here, too. So, what have you
been doing today?
>> Oh, I've just been sitting home all day.
>> Honestly, same. Let's move [music] up
front. Hatsune Miku's concert is going
to start momentarily.
>> Look, I can see her.
>> To think she would travel all the way to
Ponyville. She really is the kindest,
most sexiest pop star to ever live. I
shaved all of my hair off so I could
look like her.
>> I hear she parked her RV around back. We
should go back there after the concert
and see if she'll give us free
autographs.
>> No one was talking to you, [__] Look,
she's coming out from behind the [music]
curtain.
>> How's it going, Ponyville? Are you ready
to rock?
>> Damn, her ass is big. Imagine the size
of her poops.
>> I said, "Are you [__] ready to rock?
Yeah,
>> hurry [music] up.
>> Now that's what I like to hear. Stop the
music, twins.
[music]
>> Hey, one of you [__] throw me a rope.
I want to do some cool [__]
She's [music] flying like a Pegasus.
>> What the hell is she doing?
>> Did Did we [music] just say that at the
same time? How funny.
>> Haha. Yeah. Funny, huh? Bro,
>> really funny, sis.
>> Bro, [music] do you want to make out?
>> Friend, my sister. I would be honored to
make out with you.
Hey, hang on to the roll properly, you
dams. You're going to make me sick.
>> Every pony be mindful. She's probably
exhausted after her performance.
>> God damn. Did you hear those [__]
cheering tonight? They loved me.
>> Do you hear that?
>> It sounds like they're talking about the
concert.
>> Yeah, they were really excited to see
us.
>> Yeah, maybe we can do a do it next. What
do you say, Meiku?
>> No. They were excited for me, not your
asses.
>> Meiku, you got to calm down.
>> Yeah, we're all Vocaloids, [__]
>> You need to shut the hell up. Without
me, you [__] wouldn't be here in the
first place. And another thing, whoever
suggested a group song, you can forget
it because I'm seeing nothing but solos.
>> But then you'll be the only one getting
paid, [__]
>> Uh, yeah, that's kind of the point,
[__] Anyway,
enough talk since no one cares about you
or any of you [__] All people want
is me. Now I got to clean the [__] off
my ass. I'm going to take a ball back
because I'm Japanese and I can afford
that [__]
>> Hell yeah. I'm in the evening news,
[__]
Miku, what's this I'm hearing on the
news about you [__] all over people
at the last concert?
>> I don't know.
>> And would you mind telling me why I've
got a bunch of angry horses texting me?
>> Because the people I [__] on were
horses.
>> Miku, you can't be doing this. Think of
our image as the Vocaloids. Anything you
do will be tied back to us as well.
>> Ko, do I look like I give a [__] So
what if I land with [__] on a bunch of
horses? It's not the end of the world.
Besides, it caught me on the front
cover, did it? So, it's all Well, that
ends.
>> You mean you actually like people
knowing you only as the poop girl all
over Ponyville?
>> That's how publicity works, Kaido. You
know this [__] Or you would if you were
like me. If people want drama, you give
them drama. That's how it's always been.
>> Miku, the leader of the horses, is
called Princess Celestia. I think she's
their god or some [__] I really don't
think we should get on her bad side.
>> What is she going to do? Write a letter
to the press? She doesn't even have
fingers because she's a horse. At the
end of the day, she's no different than
the rest of them. Face it, Kaido. I won.
I always win.
>> Don't answer that. It might be the horse
got us some [__]
>> It's fine. I'll just crack the door
open. Horses can't fit through such a
small opening.
>> Greetings, blue-haired human. We are
ponies from Ponyville. We were wondering
if Miku could come out and give us
autographs.
>> It's not a good idea for you to be in
here.
>> How the hell do you three game? And
what's with the yellow one? The [__]
better not have cancer. I hear that's
contagious.
>> I shaved my hair off to look just like
you, Miku.
>> Oh, cool. I thought you just had cancer
or some [__] That would be so funny.
>> Please wait. We only want an autograph.
Are you dead ass? Well, [__] [__] You
sure just said so.
>> There. You got what you wanted. Now get
out of my RV.
>> How does it look? She didn't write your
name. She just wrote that you got some
stinky cheeks.
>> I did not. Who are you going to believe,
Twilight? One of your best friends ever
or me? Hatsune Miku.
>> Obviously Yum, Miku. You're famous.
>> Hey, look. It's the poop girl.
>> That's my name. Don't wear it out. Why
is everyone calling me poop girl?
>> Because you pooped yourself.
>> Oh yeah, I forgot about that [__]
>> Princess Celestia, what is it? Is
someone attacking [music] the castle?
No, it's far worse. I am afraid. Hatsune
Miku [music] merchandise sales are off
the charts and have even surpassed my
own. She is swaying ponies to her
[music] side in ways only a Japanese pop
idol can. As it happens, I cannot allow
such [__] to stand. Here is what I
want you to do, my [__] I want you to
go and push her RV off a cliff if my
suspicions are correct. She and her
little Vocaloids are eating lunch right
now as they prep for their next concert
this evening.
What the hell is going on? Who started
the bus?
>> It's moving by itself.
>> It's got to be those horse [__]
again. You were here. I'll go outside to
see what's up.
>> Who is it, Meiku?
>> Who do you think, Luka? It's one of
those stupid horse [__]
>> Which one?
>> How the hell should I know? The horses.
They all look the same. You can't do
this to me. I'm the Japanese pop star
sensation, Hatsune Miku. You put my tous
back where it belongs, if you know
what's good for you.
>> Yes, Miss Hatsune Miku. Whatever you
say, Hatsune Miku.
>> Twilight, as your god, I demand you
throw that turb bus off the cliff.
>> Yes, Princess Celestia. Whatever you
say, Princess Celestia.
[cheering]
>> Well, Vocaloid, I suppose this is it.
>> What do you mean, Miku? Are you saying
we're all going to die?
>> Don't talk like that, my dear darling
sister with the fat butt. We're going to
make it through this.
>> Meiku, we are going to make it through
this, aren't we? Or are the rumors going
around the RV true that [music] we're
all going to die here?
>> Ponyville is like the ghetto. Piss off
one, homie. They're all coming for your
ass.
Twilight, wait. This This isn't what it
looks [music] like. I swear. So, that's
what you snuck off to do. You were
reading a book, weren't you flawless?
[music]
It's not mine. I was just holding it for
someone. Yep. Every pony gets curious
eventually. You even folded some of the
page [music] corners so you could subtly
return to them later. That's how you
know it's a good one. Yep. I remember my
first novel. You know it's [music] okay.
Reading feels wonderful, doesn't it? You
can't just say that out loud. What if
somebody hears you? Why not? Cuz they'll
think I'm a giant nerd. Only nerds read.
Denial is a very common first stage. You
know, flawless reading doesn't make you
a nerd. It doesn't. No way. If reading
makes you happy, then you should embrace
[music] it.
>> And that's how many apples I can stick
in my dirty ass.
>> My Applejack, that [music] was quite the
um riveting presentation. I had no idea
that was, dare I say, legal in a
classroom setting. Next is Sweetie Bell
and Rarity. Please step forward.
>> Rarity, why are we hiding? You were so
excited to show them the pumpkin costume
you made. I was, but that was before I
knew Applejack was going to wear the
Apple costume I had me make for her for
career day.
>> You've been working on these outfits for
months. You said this presentation was
going to be the highlight of your whole
life and finally put your clothing
business on the map.
>> I may have been a little overly zealous,
sweetie. Now that I am aware of
Applejack's abilities, my pumpkin
costume may pale in comparison. Besides,
it doesn't even match my purple platform
stilettos. Oh, what am I going to do?
>> Wow, Rarity, that costume looks sexy as
[__] Not half bad for a pony that's 38
years old.
>> 38 years young, darling. But who's
counting? You know what, Twilight? Your
kind words give me courage. I'm going to
show the kids my new clothes line of
pumpkin themed attire. I bet this
Halloween all of Ponyville will be
dressed as pumpkins.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I won't let it end like this.
They laughed at me. Get out of my way.
>> Rarity, stop. They're just children.
You're going crazy.
>> She shot my sister.
>> Twilight blast.
>> Rarity being attacked.
>> Ghost spell that makes a hole in the
ground.
>> [music]
[screaming]
>> Every pony, put your hopes together for
our next duo, Flawless and her mom.
Well, it's our turn. I'm just going to
sneak out around back if you wouldn't
mind setting off some firecracker spells
to distract them. Actually, I want to go
in there with you. Even if it won't be
as, you know, cool as what Fractured and
Trixie have planned, I want to do it as
long as we're doing it together. I mean,
oh, flawless.
This is the place where all of the
Phillies and cults gather. The great and
powerful Trixie has to get in there
somehow. There, that open window shall
be the great and powerful Trixie's way
in.
There's so many backpacks. How will
Trixie ever know which one is flawless
and fractured? I'll just have to go
through them all and figure it out that
way. But Trixie can't hold these panties
and rummage through these children's
backpacks at the same time.
Aha! The great and powerful Trixie is a
mighty genius indeed.
Miss Cheerly, would you be so kind to
head to the back room and fetch me these
chemicals for my presentation?
>> It's a suspicious individual, Applejack.
She was in the back room stealing our
underpants.
>> You're wrong. Trixie isn't some pervert.
Flawless Fractured, I was bringing these
for you.
>> Fractured wears pink undies. That's so
girly. And look, Flawless has a kitty
cat on hers. That underwear is for
babies.
>> Those aren't ours.
>> Yeah, get away from us, you dirty panty
thief pervert.
>> You're wrong. Trixie didn't do anything
wrong. She was just bringing them their
stuff. Sparkle, say something. The great
and powerful Trixie cannot go back to
jail. We don't even know who you are.
>> Yeah, take her away. This weirdo is
making me sick.
>> Sup, [__] Today, I'd like to show
you what it's like being Princess
Celestia's most faithful student. Here
comes the lecture.
>> My job involves studying magic. But
before I became a princess, I spent most
of my life studying science as well.
>> Science? That sounds lame as hell. Yeah,
we already do that stuff every day.
>> Um, as I was saying, science helps us
understand why things happen or how
things work. And sometimes it can look
just as amazing as magic. Maybe the kids
are right. Maybe I am just boring after
all.
>> Hey now, don't start the presentation
without me.
>> Holy [__] you're Hatsune Miku.
>> I know who I am. And I'm also Twice
Funko's best friend. Tell him, [__]
>> Uh, that's right. See, as Princess
Celestia's apprentice, I get to go on
many extraordinary adventures. So,
naturally, that means getting the chance
to meet extraordinary people.
>> What the hell is taking you so long,
boy? Hurry up and take the shot. It
smells like a goddamn petting zoo up in
this [__]
>> Meiku, I can't. The gun is jammed. If
you want to kill Twilight Sparkle,
you're going to have to do it yourself
from the inside.
>> [__] are you kidding me? There's like
30 horses in here.
>> Isn't Twilight just the coolest? Maybe
next year she'll come to career day with
me so you don't have to.
>> Dear Princess Celestia, today I learned
that kids [music] are really, really
stupid. When I was little, I thought my
own parents were boring because they
were just my parents and not someone
cool like you or Hatsune [music] Miko.
Today, Twilight, look out.
>> [screaming]
>> Twilight, you have to jump.
>> I can't. The Vocaloids are down there
with guns.
>> Rarity blast.
>> [screaming]
>> That's [music] my sister. That's my big
sister.
>> God, that was so cool.
>> Rarity, you saved my life. [music]
>> Well, that settles it. Today's career
day trophy can only go to [music] one
pony. And that's how I saved my best
friend, Twilight, from the evils of
J-pop and became the most beloved big
sister in all of Ponyville for the next
two hours. [music]
We're going to do a vocal cover of Blood
on the Dance Floor, Bewitched Duet. Hope
you guys like it.
>> Let's rock this [__]
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> You're attractive.
Little witch, [music] you're beautiful.
>> Beautiful.
>> Your wickedness.
Little witch, [music]
you broke my heart.
>> Broke your heart.
>> Intruding words. Little witch, you cast
a spell.
[music]
>> Mass destroyer.
Little witch. You're beautiful.
You got me be wish cuz I'm under your
spell. Oh,
you must be a wish. Cuz I am a living
out. Oh,
now is the time, [music] now is the
hour. I am the magic. I am the power of.
All I need is one star in the sky. Wish
for you every night.
you to fall [music] in love, your little
boy.
I played with you and I was done.
[music]
Like a toy.
>> Like a toy.
>> I love I [music] destroy [singing] the
end of you.
>> The end of me.
>> So easily fooled. [music and singing]
Little boy to think it's true.
>> I'm in love with you.
You got me be wish cuz I'm under your
spell. Oh,
you must be a wish cuz I [music] am
living it out. Oh,
now is the time, now is the hour. I am
the magic. I am the power of. All I need
is one star in the sky. Wish for you.
every Now is the time. Now is the hour
to take back my heart. To take back
[music] my power. This is the moment to
break your spell. I see right through
you. Now burning hell. Now is the time.
Now is the hour to take back my [music]
heart. To take back my power. This is
the moment to break your spell.
[singing] I see [music] right through
you. No burn in hell. Now is the time.
Now is the hour to take back my heart.
To take back my tower. This is the
moment to break your spell. I see right
through you now.
>> Burning hell, [__]
>> You got me be witch cuz I'm under your
spell. Oh,
you [music] must be a witch. Cuz I am a
living.
Oh,
now is the time. Now is the hour. I am
the [music and singing] magic. I am the
power of. All I need is one star in the
sky. Wish for you every night. [singing]
[music]
>> [music]